나의
안녕하세요 여러분, 이탈리아 블로그에 오신 것을 환영합니다.
여기 처음이에요.
포시타니오에 살고 있어요.
이곳은 7일 동안 가장 좋은 친구와 함께 있어요.
이곳은 우리의 에어비앤비의 간단한 overview입니다.
정말 귀엽죠?
이 주에는 많은 일과 일정들과 유튜브 페이스들이 많이 있습니다.
그래서 즐기시길 바랍니다.
그리고 더 이상, 영상을 보도록 하겠습니다.
나는 이 ㅈㄴ 이쁘게 잘생겼다.
뭐?
지금 어떤 삶이야?
이건 진짜 미쳤어.
꿈이야.
정말 꿈이야.
진짜.
이건 런니야.
너무 맛있어.
그리고 저는 벙고리 스파게티 샀어요.
제가 타임 램프에 촬영을 했지만, 제가 첫 밥을 먹었다고요.
그리고 너무 맛있어.
너무 배불러요.
이곳은 황글리의 한가운데요 제가 지금 타임 램프로 촬영하고 있어요 근데 제가 첫 밥을 먹었거든요
너무 맛있어
너무 배고파요
이곳은 유트리덩에서 저녁을 끝냈어요 호텔에 있었어요 포사이든에 왔어요.
진짜 너무 맛있었어요.
우리가 또 한 번의 클래식 파스타를 먹었고 이제는 그냥 러시아로 가는 중이에요.
근데 솔직히 말이죠, 오늘 아침에 우린 도망가야 했죠.
15분 정도 걸리는 날이었는데 26번의 길이 될 줄은 몰랐어요.
그래서 아침에 2000번 걸었죠.
거의 다 먹었죠.
아무것도, 카페인, 물, 그리고 우리 몸이 준비가 안 됐어요.
그래서 그냥 그냥 26번의 길이 될 줄 알았죠.
그래서 그냥 올라가세요.
그리고 우리는 이 레쏘를 만들거에요.
그래서 거의 다 넘어갔어요.
제 심장이 정말 아프고 제가 돌아가야 할 것 같아요 근데 이제는 거의 다 넘어갔어요 그래서 지금 안 넘어갈 수 있어요
이제는 올라갈 수 있겠어요?
네 네, 저도 그렇게 생각해요 근데 이제는 그냥 쇼핑을 하고 카페에 가고 있어요 좀 더 쇼핑을 하고 지금 28도로 올라가고
있어요
이게 쇼핑몰이에요 인터넷에 엄청 많이 나오고 있어요 되게 귀여운 패턴이 있어요 러브샵 팬티 느낌이에요
너무 귀여워요 이렇게 여러 패턴이 있어요 다른 사이즈도 있어요 이건 작은 패턴이고 훨씬 큰 패턴이에요
이 메이크업백들 너무 좋아해요 너무 귀여워요 지난 몇 년 동안 제 원하는 패턴이 있었는데 제가 원하는 패턴이 있었어요 이렇게
귀여워요 이 패턴은 제 엄마가 만든 패턴이랑 똑같아요 그리고 78에롸스 진짜 미쳤어요 근데
메이크업 효과가 있을 것 같은데
저는 바닐라가 추천했지만 이 제품을 추천했어요 그래서 저는 이 제품을 추천했어요
너무 비싸요
안녕하세요 안녕
아, 나 눈에 띄었어?
물이 너무 깊어
이 여행을 위해 준비한 책은 We Are All Guilty by Karen Slaughter입니다 새 작품입니다 어디서 읽을지 정말 기대되는데요 제가 이미
읽은 작품은 200장 정도?
그리고 다른 책들보다 조금 다릅니다
12년 동안 엄청난 시간이 걸렸기 때문에 그 책을 읽지 못한 적이 있어요
보통 시간이 흘러서 읽을 수 있어요 그래서 제가 좋아하는지 모르겠어요
그리고 아직 책을 끝냈기 때문에 확실하게 말할 수 없네요 이제 저녁을 먹으러 갈 거예요 바지에서 씻고있어요
마크가 여기 있어요 너무 예쁘죠?
그리고 친구도 모였어요 그리고 세라!
다시 콜리나에 갔어요 너무 맛있어 뭐 샀어?
해설넛 반일도 샀어 피스테이셔도 샀어 레몬 서베
감사합니다.
🎵 Music 🎵
It's so cold!
Oh my god.
Ah, Lottie, I can't.
Okay, now that I'm in, it's not as bad.
Lottie and I just got out of the water.
And honestly, it's so fun and so refreshing.
I feel like I never am in the water.
I'm just going to do Lottie's hair care routine now.
Mediterranean octopus salad and then Lonnie got the burrata which looks so
Good.
Okay now this is our second course from lunch I got a lobster burger it looks so good and then
Lonnie got a neuronal frosting I think I'm just gonna full set
At first I only tasted the celery but the mayo or the dressing they're using is really good
I'm going
To
Make a cake.
Good morning guys, we just got ready really quickly because we're actually having a full boat day today And before
We head out, I just want to show you how I stay connected in Italy obviously to stay online with
You guys but also with my friends and family back home so thank you to saley for making this possible
Saley is an e-sim app that helps you stay connected at an affordable rate in over 200 countries around the
World and if you don't know what an e-sim is it is exactly like a normal one but it is
Digital and it just downloads into your phone and just helps you start any trip hassle free ever since I
Learned about e-sims like two or three years ago I honestly haven't gone back to a physical card because it's
Just such a hassle to get it at the airport and then you also need the pin to unlock it
In your phone and so sometimes if you don't have that on hand then it just becomes a lot more
Work and then something for you to worry about so salee is compatible with all ios and android devices and
You can just download the app and search the country or location that you're going to there are various plans
At various price points so you can just choose what is best suited for you and your trip you guys
Can get an exclusive 15 off on salee e-sim data plans you can download the salee app on the app
Store or play store and use code Brianna at checkout.
Oh, that's so
Nice.
I'm super excited and I said I was going to stop getting seafood pasta because it's the
Only thing I've been getting but I got another one.
And the boat was so much fun as well.
We took so many photos and swam so much.
I'm honestly kind of fading now, but we have a whole day ahead of us.
It's only 1.18, so I feel like gelato will perk me up.
And I forgot to show you this restaurant's view of the island.
So
Lani I made it to sorrento and before we get into anything we need to eat because we're getting hangry
And we're starving we haven't eaten since last night had dinner at 7 p.m and it is now 1 p.m
The next day so we're having a little drink before our sandwiches and then we're gonna get some cake.
Postcard shopping.
I think I'm gonna make these into prints for my wall.
Look at that red bull car.
Lottie, look!
I'm
Going to go to the bathroom.
Lani and I have left the city center of Sorrento and now we're at the beach or getting really close
So we're gonna head down and have a little beach day for the next couple of hours before coming back
For dinner and then have to take the ferry back to Positano which is where we're staying but we're super
Excited.
This is an extreme form.
We just have to climb literally down all of the rocks and then change in public in an open space
And then put our things up on a high rock so that no one can really get into them.
And they're right up there.
I'm blocking Lonnie.
The water is so blue.
I just took my hair out.
Oh my god.
People keep jumping off the rocks.
It's nice.
Oh my god, people keep jumping off the cliff.
Three, two, one!
I have to get
Down from if I want to swim.
So it doesn't seem that high, but honestly the rocks are so sharp.
It's like not even funny.
It's a little crab.
That's kind of scary.
What if it pinches my feet?
Sorry Mr.
Crab.
I'm gonna step around him.
I need to find Lonnie.
Lonnie!
Oh my gosh, oh my gosh, oh my gosh.
I
Just
Made it to Amalfi today.
We had to take the ferry at 9 a.m.
One of the earlier days that we've woken up this trip.
So now we're just going to get a little breakfast.
But I think we're going to go down a sweet treat route.
Because yesterday we had like paninis and stuff.
And that wasn't really all we wanted.
So today we're gonna get us a treat for breakfast.
This looks so good.
And then I just got orange juice and apricot cookie.
And I'm gonna eat a raspberry tart as my breakfast.
Freshly squeezed.
Super good.
There's a lot of pulp though.
Yeah there is.
So
This
Is
The first top that I tried on I really like the pattern I love red gingham as you guys probably
Know because I've been wearing it this entire trip but I just can't tell if this top kind of looks
Grumpy because it's not like cinched tight it's like loose okay this is top two
Now this is what it looks like I mean I think this one's a little bit more flattering just because
It's like tight all the way through and this is the shirt that I'm trying on I thought this tank
Top would be a little bit tighter, but it's quite loose and it's not very warm fitting.
I could probably cinch it in like this much.
So I really like this pattern.
I love blue stripes, but I don't think I'm going to get this one.
We're going into our cooking.
We made it.
Don't help.
I know, I'm sweating.
We are also 30 minutes late.
But first we're starting off with a pizza dough.
I know, I'm sweating.
We are also 30 minutes late.
But first we're starting off with a pizza dough.
I'm going to go to the bathroom.
Thank
You.
Thank you.
Thank
You.
We finished making it.
I'm going
To
Go to the bathroom.
Thank
You.
I'm going to go to the bathroom.
I'm
Going to go to the bathroom.
Thank you.